starfishfx.com 2014-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Starfishfx

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

We understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality and privacy of Your Information. By entrusting us with your information, we would like to assure you of our commitment to keep such information private. We have taken measurable steps to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of Your Information.

Starfish FX provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at www.starfishfx.com (“Site”). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

By providing us with such information, you are giving us your consent to collect, use and store the information in the manner explained hereto.

**COLLECTED DATA**

Personally Identifiable Information – When you browse the non-password protected portions of our Site, you do so anonymously; no personally identifiable information is collected. When you sign up to become a registered user of Starfish FX, we request that you provide to us your email address, a username and a password to access our Site. The law requires you to supply trading information (e.g., how long you have been trading, your preferred trading style, etc.) and a profile description. Once you register with Starfish FX and sign in to our Site, you are not anonymous to us.

As a registered user, the law requires you to provide Starfish FX with the necessary credentials to access your brokerage account (i.e. user ID, password, and information necessary to access your account). We will never access your accounts for any other purpose than to retrieve your trading data and provide the services as you have requested. You can de-activate your account for any reason at any time and we will delete all of your personally identifiable information from our servers. We will not keep a copy of your personally identifiable information for any purposes upon account deactivation except as may be required by law or to otherwise protect legal rights.

**DATA SECURITY**

When you visit our Site, we may collect information through “cookies” or other similar Web tools to enhance the user experience. Cookies are small strings of text that are sent by our Site to your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies enable us to recognize you when you return to our Site, to maintain your Web session while you browse throughout the Site, as well as help us provide you with a better, more personalized experience. Our cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but it is possible to change your browser setup so that it does not accept cookies. However, rejecting cookies may prevent you from taking advantage of certain portions of our Site.

In addition, when you are browsing our Site, Starfish FX automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the pages you request on www.starfishfx.com. We use this information to improve the functionality and usability of our services. Our log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.

We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**HOW WE USE COLLECTED DATA**

Customer Service – Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us during the registration process, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your account. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account.

Brokerage Information – As a registered user of our Site, you may provide to us the credentials to access your brokerage account to retrieve your trading data. This information is only used to obtain trading history for your account and this information and is not accessible anywhere on our Site.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * **We Do Not Reveal Any Personally Identifiable Information.**

We will not publish any personally identifiable information (e.g. name, email address or contact information) on our Site for others to view, without your permission, unless you choose to post it yourself on the Site.

  * **We Do Not Rent or Share Any Personally Identifiable Information**

Starfish FX does not rent or share any personally identifiable information with third parties that are not our agents or service providers.

  * **We May Provide Your Information If Legally Required**

Starfish FX may be required to provide your information under the following circumstances: in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against actual or threatened legal claims. In addition when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or activities which we believe give rise to legal liability to us, our members or third parties, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Starfish FX terms of business, or as otherwise required by law.

**PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 18**

In compliance with most national legal systems, we do not permit persons under age of 18 years to become users, and we will not collect information from persons under the age of 18. By using our Site, you represent that you are over the age of 18.

**FINAL STATEMENT**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [cs@starfishfx.com](mailto:cs@starfishfx.com).

This Policy is subject to change without notice. For this reason you are advised to look for updates from time to time.
